Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.13
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Attorney General of the United States, 1988-1991; XIII.
  - News Clippings, 14.
    - Summaries: AM/PM News
      - Summaries: AM/PM News, August-September, 1988 (Box 869, Folder 1)
      - Summaries: AM/PM News, October-November,1988 (Box 869, Folder 2)
      - Summaries: AM/PM News, December, 1988-January, 1989 (Box 869, Folder 3)
      - Summaries: AM/PM News, February-March, 1989 (Box 869, Folder 4)
      - Summaries: AM/PM News, April-May, 1989 (Box 869, Folder 5)
      - Summaries: AM/PM News, June-July, 1989 (Box 869, Folder 6)
      - Summaries: AM/PM News, August-September, 1989 (Box 869, Folder 7)
      - Summaries: AM/PM News, October-November, 1989 (Box 869, Folder 8)
      - Summaries: AM/PM News, December, 1989-January, 1990 (Box 869, Folder 9)
      - Summaries: AM/PM News, February-March, 1990 (Box 869, Folder 10)
      - Summaries: AM/PM News, April-May, 1990 (Box 870, Folder 1)
      - Summaries: AM/PM News, June-July, 1990 (Box 870, Folder 2)
      - Summaries: AM/PM News, August-September, 1990 (Box 870, Folder 3)
      - Summaries: AM/PM News, October-November, 1990 (Box 870, Folder 4)
      - Summaries: AM/PM News, December, 1990-January,1991 (Box 870, Folder 5)
      - Summaries: AM/PM News, February-March, 1991 (Box 870, Folder 6)
      - Summaries: AM/PM News, April-May,1991 (Box 870, Folder 7)
      - Summaries: AM/PM News, June-July, 1991 (Box 870, Folder 8)
      - Summaries: AM/PM News, August 1-16, 1991 (Box 870, Folder 9)
    - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, July 12-August 12, 1988 (Box 871, Folder 1-12)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, August 15-September 23, 1988 (Box 872, Folder 1-12)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, September 26-November 4, 1988 (Box 873, Folder 1-12)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, November 7-December 9, 1988 (Box 874, Folder 1-10)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, December 12, 1988-January 10, 1989 (Box 875, Folder 1-9)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, January 11-February 3, 1989 (Box 876, Folder 1-7)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, February 6-March 10, 1989 (Box 877, Folder 1-10)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, March 13-April 7, 1989 (Box 878, Folder 1-9)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, April 10-May 5, 1989 (Box 879, Folder 1-8)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, May 8-June 15, 1989 (Box 880, Folder 1-8)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, June 16-July 14, 1989 (Box 881, Folder 1-8)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, July 17-August 10, 1989 (Box 882, Folder 1-7)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, August 11-September 11, 1989 (Box 883, Folder 1-8)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, September 12-October 11, 1989 (Box 884, Folder 1-8)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, October 12-November 15, 1989 (Box 885, Folder 1-8)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, November 16-December 20,1989 (Box 886, Folder 1-8)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, December 21, 1989-January 24, 1990 (Box 887, Folder 1-8)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, January 25-February 26, 1990 (Box 888, Folder 1-7)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, February 27-March 30, 1990 (Box 889, Folder 1-8)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, April 2-May 4, 1990 (Box 890, Folder 1-8)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, May 7-June 7, 1990 (Box 891, Folder 1-8)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, June 8-July 2,1990 (Box 892, Folder 1-7)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, July 3-27, 1990 (Box 893, Folder 1-7)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, July 30-September 11, 1990 (Box 894, Folder 1-8)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, September 12-October 18, 1990 (Box 895, Folder 1-7)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, October 19-November 26, 1990 (Box 896, Folder 1-8)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, November 27, 1990-January 11, 1991 (Box 897, Folder 1-8)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, January 14-March 5, 1991 (Box 898, Folder 1-8)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, March 6-April 16,1991 (Box 899, Folder 1-8)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, April 17-May 30, 1991 (Box 900, Folder 1-8)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, May 31-July 11, 1991 (Box 901, Folder 1-10)
      - Daily Clippings: AM/PM News, July 12-August 16, 1991 (Box 902, Folder 1-9)
    - Burelles
      - Burelles, October, 1988-March 29, 1989 (Box 903, Folder 1-8)
      - Burelles, March 29-August 16, 1989 (Box 904, Folder 1-9)
      - Burelles, August 18, 1989-January 6, 1990 (Box 905, Folder 1-10)
      - Burelles, January 7-July 13, 1990 (Box 906, Folder 1-12)
      - Burelles, July 12-November, 1990 (Box 907, Folder 1-10)
    - Pennsylvania Clippings
      - Pennsylvania Clippings, September, 1989-March, 1990 (Box 907, Folder 11)
  - Reports, 15.
    Reports issued by various DOJ components have been grouped in this section for easy reference. Many of them have been digitized and are available here online. These cover a broad arrange of subjects and are excellence sources of information.
    Topics include, for example: DEA, crime prevention, DOJ legal activities, Project Triggerlock, civil justice reform, 200th Anniversary of the Office of Attorney General, Attorney General Annual Reports, reports to Congress, financial institution fraud, response to violent crime, savings and loan scandal, drug trafficking, reports to the President, accomplishments of the department, Americans with Disabilities Act, Public Integrity Section reports, FBI reports, terrorism, white collar crime, firearms, criminal history information, Bureau of Justice statistics, DNA profiling, organized crime, U.S. Attorneys, U.S. Marshals, and Operation Weed and Seed.
    The AG reports are filed in alphabetical order according to the issuing department or office. Within each department, the reports are filed chronologically. The date range is 1989-1991. Some of the offices are for example: Office of Attorney General, FBI, Department of Justice, DEA, and Civil Division. Each office or department produced several publications and/or periodicals, a number of which are among the items available here online. When searching these reports, it will be useful to be familiar with commonly used department abbreviations, or refer to our collections list of abbreviations.
    - Department of Justice (DOJ)
      - "Coordination between DEA and the FBI: A Report to the Chairman, Committee on Governmental Affairs, U.S. Senate", March, 1990 (Box 908, Folder 1)
      - "Crime Prevention in American: Call to Action," Crime Prevention Coalition, 1990 (Box 908, Folder 2)
      - "Crime Prevention in America: Foundations for Action," Crime Prevention Coalition, 1990 (Box 908, Folder 3)
      - DOJ Employee Ethics Handbook, 1st edition, 1989 (Box 908, Folder 4)
      - DOJ Employee Ethics Handbook, 2nd edition, May, 1990 (Box 908, Folder 5)
      - "United States Department of Justice Legal Activities", 1989-1990 (Box 908, Folder 6)
      - "United States Department of Justice Legal Activities", 1990-1991 (Box 908, Folder 7)
      - "United States Department of Justice Legal Activities", 1991-1992 (Box 908, Folder 8)
      - "Prison Crowding and Court-Ordered Population Caps: Report to the President 1990", March, 1991 (Box 908, Folder 9)
      - "Project Triggerlock: Incarcerating the Armed Criminal--Year One: May, 1991-April, 1992", July, 1992 (Box 908, Folder 10)
      - "Agenda for Civil Justice Reform in America: Report from the President's Council on Competitiveness", August, 1991 (Box 908, Folder 11)
    - Antitrust Division
      - "Antitrust Enforcement Guidelines for International Operations", November 10, 1988 (Box 908, Folder 12)
    - Attorney General, Office of (OAG)
      - "200th Anniversary of the Office of the Attorney General: 1789-1989", 1990 (Box 908, Folder 13)
      - "Annual Report of the Attorney General of the United States", 1988 (Box 908, Folder 14)
      - "Annual Report of the Attorney General of the United States", 1989 (Box 908, Folder 15)
      - "Annual Report of the Attorney General of the United States", 1990 (Box 908, Folder 16)
      - "Annual Report of the Attorney General of the United States", 1991 (Box 908, Folder 17)
      - "Annual Report of the Department of Justice Asset Forfeiture Program", 1990 (Box 908, Folder 18)
      - "Attacking Financial Institution Fraud: Annual Report to the Congress of the United States", 1991 (Box 908, Folder 19)
      - "Attacking Financial Institution Fraud: Annual Report to the Congress of the United States", 1992 (Box 908, Folder 20)
      - "Attacking Organized Crime: 1991 National Strategy, 1990 Program Report", January, 1991 (Box 908, Folder 21)
      - "Attacking Savings and Loan Institution Fraud", December 31, 1990 (Box 908, Folder 22)
      - "Attorney General's Semiannual Report on Audit Resolution", November 30, 1989 (Box 908, Folder 23)
      - "Attorney General's Semiannual Report on Audit Resolution", May 31, 1990 (Box 908, Folder 24)
      - "Attorney General's Semiannual Management Report to Congress: April 1, 1990-September 30, 1990", November 28, 1990 (Box 908, Folder 25)
      - "Attorney General's Semiannual Management Report to Congress: October 1, 1990-March 31, 1991" (Box 908, Folder 26)
      - "Attorney General's Summit on Law Enforcement Responses to Violent Crime: Public Safety in the Nineties" (Conference Summary), March 3-5, 1991 (Box 908, Folder 27)
      - "Bulletin on Economic Crime Enforcement" Vol. 8, No. 4, 1989 (Box 908, Folder 28)
      - "Drug Trafficking: A Report to the President of the United States", August 3, 1989 (Box 908, Folder 29)
      - "Justice," Vol. 1, No. 1, Spring, 1991 (Box 908, Folder 30)
      - "On Course and Getting Results: A Report to the President of the United States", April 1, 1990 (Box 908, Folder 31)
      - "Toward a Safer America: The Justice Department's Record of Accomplishment in the First 2 Years of the Bush Administration ", March, 1991 (Box 908, Folder 32)
      - "Toward a Safer America: The Justice Department's Record of Accomplishment in the First 2 Years of the Bush Administration " (slightly different than above), March, 1991 (Box 908, Folder 33)
    - Bureau of Prisons
      - "Bureau of Prisons GOALS for 1991... and Beyond" (Box 908, Folder 34)
      - "Federal Prisons Journal," Vol. 1, Nos. 1-4 and Vol. 2, No. 1, Summer, 1989-Winter, 1991 (Box 908, Folder 35-39)
    - Civil Division
      - "Cases: Civil Division's Case Management System", July, 1988 (Box 908, Folder 40)
      - "Expertise in the Civil Division", July 10, 1990 (Box 908, Folder 41)
      - "Civil Division: Recruiting Booklet", March, 1990 (Box 908, Folder 42)
      - "Civil Division: Recruiting Booklet", September, 1990 (Box 908, Folder 43)
      - "Civil Action," Vol. 1, No. 4, September, 1990 (Box 908, Folder 44)
    - Civil Rights Division
      - "The Americans with Disabilities Act Requirements Fact Sheet", 1990 (Box 908, Folder 45)
      - "The Americans with Disabilities Act", 1990 (Box 908, Folder 46)
      - "The Americans with Disabilities Act: Questions and Answers", 1990 (Box 908, Folder 47)
      - "The Civil Liberties Act of 1988: Questions and Answers" (Box 908, Folder 48)
    - Community Relations Service
      - "Annual Report of the Community Relations Service", 1989 (Box 908, Folder 49)
      - "Annual Report of the Community Relations Service", 1990 (Box 908, Folder 50)
    - Criminal Division
      - "Federal Prosecution of Election Offenses," 5th edition, May, 1988 (Box 909, Folder 1)
      - "Fraud Section Report of Activities: Fiscal Year 1989" (Box 909, Folder 2)
      - "Fraud Section Report of Activities: Fiscal Year 1990" (Box 909, Folder 3)
      - "Report to Congress on the Activities and Operations of the Public Integrity Section for 1987", July, 1988 (Box 909, Folder 4)
    - Drug Enforcement Administration (DEA)
      - "DEA: Briefing Book", June, 1991 (Box 909, Folder 5)
      - "Clandestinely Produced Drugs, Analogues and Precursors: Problems and Solutions," Proceedings of an international conference on assessment of drug control issues, Rabat, Morocco, 1989 (Box 909, Folder 6)
      - "DEA World," Vol. 2, No. 7, March- April, 1989 (Box 909, Folder 7)
      - "1988 Domestic Cannabis Eradication/Suppression Program Final Report", December, 1988 (Box 909, Folder 8)
      - "Drug Abuse Prevention for Explorers: A Guidebook," Boy Scouts of America Exploring Division, ca. 1990 (Box 909, Folder 9)
      - "Drugs of Abuse", 1988 (Box 909, Folder 10)
      - "Microgram," Vol. 22, No. 1, January, 1989 (Box 909, Folder 11)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI)
      - "Drug Report", 1988 (Box 909, Folder 12)
      - "FBI Mission: To Uphold the Law", March, 1990 (Box 909, Folder 13)
      - "Forensic Science Research and Training Center, FBI Laboratory: Annual Report, 1987", 1988 (Box 909, Folder 14)
      - "Impact of FBI Investigations on Crimes of Violence: Violent Crimes and Major Offenders Section", January, 1991 (Box 909, Folder 15)
      - "Law Enforcement Bulletin" Volumes 58-60 (incomplete), January, 1989-August, 1991 (Box 909, Folder 16-44)
      - "The Investigator", February-March, 1989 (Box 909, Folder 45-46)
      - "The Investigator", April, 1989-August, 1991 (Box 910, Folder 1-6)
      - "Terrorism in the United States, 1987", December 31, 1987 (Box 910, Folder 7-9)
      - "White-Collar Crime: A Report to the Public", 1989 (Box 910, Folder 10)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS)
      - "Commissioner's Communique" Vol. 11, No. 3, Vol. 12, Nos. 3-5, and Vol. 13, No. 1, May, 1988-February, 1990 (Box 910, Folder 11-15)
      - "INS Reporter: Working for a Better America: Special Report on the Implementation of the Immigration Reform and Control Act of 1986," Vol. 35, January, 1988 (Box 910, Folder 16)
      - "1987 Statistical Yearbook of the Immigration and Naturalization Service", October, 1988 (Box 910, Folder 17)
    - Inspector General, Office of
      - "Office of Inspector General Semiannual Report to Congress: April 14, 1989-September 30, 1989", October 25, 1989 (Box 910, Folder 18)
      - "Office of Inspector General Semiannual Report to Congress: October 1, 1989-March 3, 1990", April 30, 1990 (Box 910, Folder 19)
      - "Office of Inspector General Semiannual Report to Congress: April 1, 1990-September 30, 1990", October 31, 1990 (Box 910, Folder 20)
      - "Office of Inspector General Semiannual Report to Congress: October 1, 1990-March 31, 1991", April 30, 1991 (Box 910, Folder 21)
    - Justice Programs, Office of
      - "Annual Report of the Office of Justice Program: Fiscal Year 1989" (Box 910, Folder 22)
      - "Annual Report of the Office of Justice Program: Fiscal Year 1990" (Box 910, Folder 23)
      - "Fiscal Year 1990 Program Plan: BJA, BJS, NIJ, OJJDP, OVC", March, 1990 (Box 910, Folder 24)
      - "Report of the Assistant Attorney General, Fiscal Year 1988", March 3, 1989 (Box 910, Folder 25)
      - "Report to the Attorney General on Systems for Identifying Felons Who Attempt to Purchase Firearms", October, 1989 (Box 910, Folder 26)
      - "Bureau of Justice Assistance Drug Recognition Program: Monograph", April, 1989 (Box 910, Folder 27)
      - "Edward Byrne Memorial State and Local Law Enforcement Assistance Program: Fiscal Year 1991 Discretionary Program Application Kit," Bureau of Justice Assistance, February 20, 1991 (Box 910, Folder 28)
      - "Implementing Project DARE (Drug Abuse Resistance Education): Implementation Manual," Bureau of Justice Assistance, June, 1988 (Box 910, Folder 29)
      - "An Invitation to Project DARE (Drugs Abuse Resistance Education): Program Brief," Bureau of Justice Assistance, June, 1988 (Box 910, Folder 30)
      - "Fiscal Year 1988 Report on Drug Control," Bureau of Justice Assistance (Box 910, Folder 31)
      - "Fiscal Year 1988 Report on Drug Control: Executive Summary," Bureau of Justice Assistance, 1989 (Box 910, Folder 32)
      - "Attorney General's Program for Improving the Nation's Criminal History Records and Identifying Felons Who Attempt to Purchase Firearms: Overview," Bureau of Justice Statistics, March, 1991 (Box 910, Folder 33)
      - "Criminal Justice Information Policy: Survey of Criminal History Information Systems," Bureau of Justice Statistics, March, 1991 (Box 910, Folder 34)
      - "Drugs and Crime Facts, 1988," Bureau of Justice Statistics, September, 1989 (Box 910, Folder 35)
      - "Drugs and Crime Facts, 1990," Bureau of Justice Statistics, 1991 (Box 910, Folder 36)
      - "Bureau of Justice Statistics National Update," Vol. 1, No. 1, July, 1991 (Box 910, Folder 37)
      - "Special Report: Drug Use and Crime," Bureau of Justice Statistics, December, 1989 (Box 910, Folder 38)
      - "Violent Crime in the United States," Bureau of Justice Statistics, March, 1991 (Box 910, Folder 39)
      - National Institute of Justice: Construction Bulletin, "Correctional Needs Met by Federal Surplus Property", March, 1990 (Box 910, Folder 40)
      - "National Institute of Justice Evaluation Plan: 1991", June, 1991 (Box 910, Folder 41)
      - NIJ Reports: "Cracking down on street drugs: New strategies," No. 213, March-April, 1989 (Box 910, Folder 42)
      - NIJ Reports: a Bimonthly Journal of the National Institute of Justice No. 217, November- December, 1989 (Box 910, Folder 43)
      - NIJ: Research in Action: "The Courts: Current Federal Research", 1989 (Box 910, Folder 44)
      - "National Institute of Justice Research Plan: 1991", May, 1991 (Box 910, Folder 45)
      - "Searching for Answers: Research and Evaluation on Drugs and Crime," Report to the President, the Attorney General, and the Congress by the National Institute of Justice, July, 1990 (Box 911, Folder 1)
      - "Searching for Answers: Annual Evaluation Report on Drugs and Crime," A Report to the President, the Attorney General, and the Congress by the National Institute of Justice, April, 1991 (Box 911, Folder 2)
      - "DNA Profiling: For Positive Identification," A Technology Assessment Program Bulletin from the National Institute of Justice, September, 1990 (Box 911, Folder 3)
    - Legal Counsel, Office of
      - "Opinions of the Office of Legal Counsel: Consisting of Selected Memorandum Opinions Advising the President of the United States, The Attorney General and Other Executive Officers of the Federal Government in Relation to Their Official Duties," Vol. 12, 1988 (Box 911, Folder 4)
      - "Opinions of the Office of Legal Counsel: Consisting of Selected Memorandum Opinions Advising the President of the United States, The Attorney General and Other Executive Officers of the Federal Government in Relation to Their Official Duties," Vol. 13, 1989 (Box 911, Folder 5)
      - "Opinions of the Office of Legal Counsel: Consisting of Selected Memorandum Opinions Advising the President of the United States, The Attorney General and Other Executive Officers of the Federal Government in Relation to Their Official Duties," Vol. 14, 1990 (Box 911, Folder 6)
      - "Opinions of the Office of Legal Counsel: Consisting of Selected Memorandum Opinions Advising the President of the United States, The Attorney General and Other Executive Officers of the Federal Government in Relation to Their Official Duties," Vol. 15, 1991 (Box 911, Folder 7)
    - National Drug Control Policy
      - "Leading Drug Indicators: An Office of National Drug Control Policy White Paper", September, 1990 (Box 911, Folder 8)
      - "National Drug Control Strategy," The White House, January, 1990 (Box 911, Folder 9)
      - "National Drug Control Strategy: Budget Summary," The White House, February, 1991 (Box 911, Folder 10)
    - National Drug Policy Board
      - "Toward a Drug-Free America: The National Drug Strategy and Implementation Plans," A Report from the National Drug Policy Board, 1988 (Box 911, Folder 11)
    - Organized Crime
      - "Annual Report of the Organized Crime Drug Enforcement Task Force Program, Fiscal Year 1988", March 31, 1989 (Box 911, Folder 12)
    - Professional Responsibility, Office of
      - "Annual Report to the Attorney General", 1988 (Box 911, Folder 13)
    - Tax Division
      - "United States Department of Justice Tax Division", March, 1990 (Box 911, Folder 14)
    - US Attorneys, Office of
      - US Attorneys: "For Your Information" Vol. 8, No. 11, August, 1988 (Box 911, Folder 15)
      - "Network News" Vol. 4, No. 6, Law Enforcement Coordinating Committee/Victim-Witness of Executive Office for United States Attorneys, November- December, 1988 (Box 911, Folder 16)
      - "Network News" Vol. 5, No. 3, Law Enforcement Coordinating Committee/Victim-Witness of Executive Office for United States Attorneys, March, 1989 (Box 911, Folder 17)
      - "Network News" Vol. 5, No. 4, Law Enforcement Coordinating Committee/Victim-Witness of Executive Office for United States Attorneys, April, 1989 (Box 911, Folder 18)
      - "Network News" Vol. 5, No. 5, Law Enforcement Coordinating Committee/Victim-Witness of Executive Office for United States Attorneys, May, 1989 (Box 911, Folder 19)
      - "Network News" Vol. 5, No. 7, Law Enforcement Coordinating Committee/Victim-Witness of Executive Office for United States Attorneys, July, 1989 (Box 911, Folder 20)
      - "Network News" Vol. 5, No. 8, Law Enforcement Coordinating Committee/Victim-Witness of Executive Office for United States Attorneys, August, 1989 (Box 911, Folder 21)
      - "Network News" Vol. 5, No. 9, Law Enforcement Coordinating Committee/Victim-Witness of Executive Office for United States Attorneys, September, 1989 (Box 911, Folder 22)
      - "Network News" Vol. 5, No. 10, Law Enforcement Coordinating Committee/Victim-Witness of Executive Office for United States Attorneys, October, 1989 (Box 911, Folder 23)
      - "Network News" Vol. 5, No. 11, Law Enforcement Coordinating Committee/Victim-Witness of Executive Office for United States Attorneys, November, 1989 (Box 911, Folder 24)
      - "Network News" Vol. 5, No. 12, Law Enforcement Coordinating Committee/Victim-Witness of Executive Office for United States Attorneys, December, 1989 (Box 911, Folder 25)
      - "Network News" Vol. 6, No. 1, Law Enforcement Coordinating Committee/Victim-Witness of Executive Office for United States Attorneys, January, 1990 (Box 911, Folder 26)
      - "Network News" Vol. 6, No. 4, Law Enforcement Coordinating Committee/Victim-Witness of Executive Office for United States Attorneys, April, 1990 (Box 911, Folder 27)
      - "Network News" Vol. 7, No. 3, Law Enforcement Coordinating Committee/Victim-Witness of Executive Office for United States Attorneys, March, 1991 (Box 911, Folder 28)
      - "Network News" Vol. 7, No. 7, Law Enforcement Coordinating Committee/Victim-Witness of Executive Office for United States Attorneys, July, 1991 (Box 911, Folder 29)
      - "Murphy's Law," Vol. 4, No. 8, Executive Office for US Attorneys, August, 1988 (Box 911, Folder 30)
      - "Murphy's Law," Vol. 6, No. 2, Executive Office for US Attorneys, March-April, 1990 (Box 911, Folder 31)
    - United States Marshals Service
      - "The Director's Report: A Review of the United States Marshals Service in Fiscal Year 1989", 1990 (Box 911, Folder 32)
      - "Outline of US Marshals Service Activities: 1990" (Box 911, Folder 33)
      - "The Pentacle," Vol. 8, No. 1 and Vol. 9, No. 1, February, 1988, June, 1989 (Box 911, Folder 34-35)
      - "The Pentacle," Bicentennial Edition, Vol. 9, No. 2, September, 1989 (Box 911, Folder 36)
    - United States Parole Commission
      - "Annual Report of the United States Parole Commission: October 1, 1987 to September 30, 1988", January 1, 1989 (Box 911, Folder 37)
    - Weed and Seed, Office of
      - "Operation Weed and Seed: Reclaiming America's Neighborhoods," Report to Congress, March 25, 1993 (Box 911, Folder 38)